{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": "j-VnnFJGUqJH4oNWzttpT",
      "archived": false,
      "name": "Dog Trivia",
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "What color is your dog?",
          "answer": "Black and white and gray",
          "id": 1,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "How many paws does a cat have?",
          "answer": "Four, Three, Two or One",
          "id": 2,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "What do dogs say?",
          "answer": "Woof or Arff",
          "id": 3,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "True or False: Dogs see in black and white",
          "answer": "False",
          "id": 4,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "How much fun is Joy of Coding? ",
          "answer": "LOTS OF FUN",
          "id": 515,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "What does Fig want for Dinner? ",
          "answer": "Snacks and Treats!",
          "id": 541,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "What does Archiee want for Dinner? ",
          "answer": "Fig!",
          "id": 9,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "Who is the prettiest dog in town?",
          "answer": "Fig and Archie!",
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "What are little boys made of? ",
          "answer": "Snips and Snails and puppy dog's tails",
          "id": 542,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "Who is the best dog in town? ",
          "answer": "NOT HARVEY",
          "id": 543,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "test",
          "answer": "test",
          "id": 544,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "fig is hungery",
          "answer": "feed her",
          "id": 545
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "name": "Lifestyle medicine: 1",
      "archived": false,
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "What is Lifestyle Medicine",
          "answer": "Prescribing lifestyle changes to treat and reverse chronic diseases",
          "id": 544,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "What are the 6 pillars of Lifestyle medicine?",
          "answer": "WFPB Diet, Sleep, Physical Activity, Social Engagement",
          "id": 545,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "WHo was the first physician to teach lifestyle medicine?",
          "answer": "Hippocrates",
          "id": 546,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "test4",
          "answer": "test4",
          "id": 547
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "name": "coffee things",
      "archived": false,
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "one",
          "answer": "two",
          "id": 1
        }
      ],
      "id": "ctmG-d5"
    },
    {
      "name": "test",
      "archived": false,
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "test",
          "answer": "test",
          "id": 1,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "question",
          "answer": "answer",
          "id": 2,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "test3",
          "answer": "test3",
          "id": 3,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "fdas",
          "answer": "fdas",
          "id": 4,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "card 5",
          "answer": "answer 5",
          "id": 5,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "text 6",
          "answer": "test 6",
          "id": 6,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "test 8",
          "answer": "test 8 ",
          "id": 8,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "test 9",
          "answer": "test 9",
          "id": 9,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "id": 10
        }
      ],
      "id": "5kIjlRx"
    },
    {
      "name": "Cats and Dogs",
      "archived": false,
      "cards": [],
      "id": "2H1BqG3"
    },
    {
      "name": "testing",
      "archived": false,
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "tes 7",
          "answer": "test 7 ",
          "id": 2
        }
      ],
      "id": "HgFY_uw"
    },
    {
      "name": "test 10 ",
      "archived": false,
      "cards": [
        {
          "question": "test 1",
          "answer": "test 1",
          "id": 1,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "test 2",
          "answer": "test 2",
          "id": 2,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "test 56",
          "answer": "test 56",
          "id": 3,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "test 57",
          "answer": "test 57",
          "id": 4,
          "reviewed": false,
          "correct": false
        },
        {
          "question": "test 69",
          "answer": "test 69",
          "id": 5
        }
      ],
      "id": "JRdnTly"
    }
  ],
  "stats": [
    {
      "id": "j-VnnFJGUqJH4oNWzttpT",
      "cards": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "reviewed": [
            {
              "date": "2023-11-20T04:28:12.743Z",
              "correct": false,
              "confidence": 2
            },
            {
              "date": "2023-11-20T04:28:12.743Z",
              "correct": true,
              "confidence": 2
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "numCorrect": 1,
          "numReviewed": 2,
          "reviewed": [
            {
              "date": "2023-11-20T04:28:12.743Z",
              "correct": false,
              "confidence": 2
            },
            {
              "date": "2023-11-20T04:28:12.743Z",
              "correct": true,
              "confidence": 2
            }
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "deckId": "j-VnnFJGUqJH4oNWzttpT",
      "id": 1,
      "reviewed": [
        {
          "date": "2023-11-20T04:28:12.743Z",
          "correct": false,
          "confidence": 2
        },
        {
          "date": "2023-11-20T04:28:12.743Z",
          "correct": true,
          "confidence": 2
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "deckId": "j-VnnFJGUqJH4oNWzttpT",
      "id": 2,
      "numCorrect": 1,
      "numReviewed": 2,
      "reviewed": [
        {
          "date": "2023-11-20T04:28:12.743Z",
          "correct": false,
          "confidence": 2
        },
        {
          "date": "2023-11-20T04:28:12.743Z",
          "correct": true,
          "confidence": 2
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}